http://www.heavyharmonies.com/cgi-bin/privacy.cgi

HeavyHarmonies.Com
BrutalMetal.Com
HeavensMetal.Com
Want to talk rock and metal? Come join the Heavy Harmonies message board!
Site Login
Message Board!
My CD Collection
View Bands by Genre:
Pop AOR / Westcoast (423)
Melodic Rock / AOR (1973)
80s Hard Rock (4345)
Modern Hard Rock (193)
Sleaze Glam (751)
Melodic Metal (698)
Prog Rock (251)
Southern or Blues Rock (154)
Instrumental Wizards (181)
Search ALL of Heavy Harmonies:
Search specific categories:
ArtistAlbum TitleSong TitleRecord LabelYear Released
THE Hard Rock and AOR Reference on the Internet!
Bands: 8971
CDS: 21296     Songs: 252604
September 12, 2020:
Two Weeks Into the Annual Heavy Harmonies Donation Drive!
We're two weeks into the annual donation drive, a month left to go, and donations stand at covering 33% of the site's annual out-of-pocket expenses. Most
of the regular donors have already contributed, so I'm asking that if
you find the site useful and enjoyable, please consider kicking in $10 or
$20 a year. It keeps the site free for everyone and no annoying off-topic ads or ad-blocker
nag messages.
Donation buttons are shown below. There is a thread on the HH forum that explains the perks for donating at the $20 and $50 levels.
Thank you for supporting the Heavy Harmonies community!
-Dan
Your ongoing support of Heavy Harmonies is appreciated!
Privacy Policy
Last updated March 22, 2019
The success of Heavy Harmonies depends upon our ability
to maintain the trust of our users. Below is information
regarding our commitment to protect the privacy of
users.
Heavy Harmonies has created this privacy statement in order to
demonstrate our firm commitment to viewers' privacy. The following
paragraphs disclose our information gathering and dissemination
practices for the Heavy Harmonies website:
Email Addresses
When you choose to submit information for inclusion in the Heavy
Harmonies database, your email address is requested for contact purposes.
Also, when you register to add comments to the CD pages on the site, you
are asked to provide your email address.
Your email address will not be given out, traded, or sold to third
parties.
Cookies
Your web browser will store information about
Heavy Harmonies to make your visit more convenient:
(1) when you change your setting for the display of the band pages,
that setting is stored in your browser so it is remembered on your
next visit, and (2) when you login to leave comments, your login and
password are stored in your web browser so you do not have to re-enter them.
You have the option of blocking the use of
Cookies by changing a setting in your web browser. Please see your browser
supplier's Web site for details on how to do this.
Logs
We use log files
to collect Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet
service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, and date/time
stamp. We use this information to analyze site usage, administer the site,
understand usage and navigation trends, and determine the
viability of content. This information, is NOT linked to any
personally identifiable information.
Links
This site contains links to other sites. Heavy Harmonies is not responsible
for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites.
Compensated Affiliate Links
There are affiliate links on this website, if you click those links and make a purchase I may receive an affiliate commission.
Disclosure: Heavy Harmonies is a participant in the eBay Partner Network, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to eBay.com.
Contact
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this
(See all...)
(See all...)
© 1998-2020. All rights reserved.
Privacy Policy
Top
